__rmul__(self, value, /)
    Return value*self.
|
sort(self, /, *, key=None, reverse=False)
    Sort the list in ascending order and return None.
|
    The sort is in-place (i.e. the list itself is modified) and stable (i.e. the
    order of two equal elements is maintained).
|
    If a key function is given, apply it once to each list item and sort them,
    ascending or descending, according to their function values.
|
    The reverse flag can be set to sort in descending order.
|